<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
The Bible was written so we could believe in Jesus. (John 20:31)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
BibleTime includes a really useful handbook written by Fred Saalbach.
To read it choose the item "Handbook" in the "Help" menu of BibleTime.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
No one is allowed by God to add anything to or take anything away from the Word. (Revelation 22:18-19)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
The Bible is like a mirror. (James 1:23)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
BibleTime does include a <B>Bible Study HowTo</B>!
It was written by Bob Harman and is a great introduction how to study the Bible.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
You can save, print and copy the whole search result by pressing the right mouse button on the icon of the searched module in the search dialog.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
The Bible is our only spiritual weapon. (Ephesians 6:17)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
To get the number of verses in the Bible search for a space in the module.
The search analysis shows you the number of verses of each book.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
The Bible is truth. (John 17:17)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
If you would like to create a set of bookmarks around a specific topic with comments containing what the Lord told you here, it's best to
make bookmarks from your personal commentary.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
The scriptures give us the wisdom that leads to salvation. (2 Timothy 3:15)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
To lookup the meaning of the original hebrew or greek word in a Bible supporting Strong's numbers, switch them on and 
click on the strong number. Now a new window showing the strong number with
it's explanation is shown. If your favourite translation doesn't support Strong's numbers please refer to an alternate translation for the number of the corresponding word.
Make sure you have set the default modules in the preferences.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
If you want to use a commentary as a topical reference, search it for terms your topic is about.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
In the beginning was the Word, the Word was with God, and the Word was God. (John 1:1)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
We will be judged on the last day by the words Jesus spoke. (John 12:48)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
If you want to find the full set of verses or entries on a area of content, you should use the option "Multiple words (OR)" for searching.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
If you are searching a verse you know only fuzzy or in a different translation search for the most probable terms in multiple Bible translations at the same time.
</html></tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
God's Word can be a lamp to your feet and a light to your path. (Psalm 119:105)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
If you want to search a word in a foreign module (e.g. greek or hebrew), open a display window and choose a chapter or an entry which contains this word.
Select it and copy it to the clipboard. Now insert the copied word in the search text box of the searchdialog.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
The Word of God will not return to Him without accomplishing its purpose. (Isaiah 55:11)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
Foreign modules do often require a special font to display correctly. You can set the font for each language in the preferences.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
Did you know that the first book ever printed on a printing press was the Bible (by Johann Gutenberg, in 1492)?
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
God has already given to us everything pertaining to life and godliness. (2 Peter 1:3)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
All important elements of BibleTime's graphical user interface have a tooltip and a "What's this?" help.<BR>
To read the "What's this?" help press the keys SHIFT+F1 and click on the part.
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
The Word of God is living, active, and sharper than any two-edged sword. (Hebrews 4:12)
</html>
</tip>

<tip category="BibleTime|General">
<html>
You are using a program that has been written for the glory of God.<BR>May He bless you as you study His Word!
</html>
</tip>


